atgear.com 2009-06-21

# Tobacco Education Clearinghouse of California -

Privacy Policy 

This privacy policy covers the site [http://www.tobaccofreecatalog.org](http://www.tobaccofreecatalog.org/) and [http://www.tecc.org](http://www.tecc.org/). Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to our users’ privacy, we disclose the following information.

> 1\. What personally identifiable information ETR Associates collects.
> 
> 2\. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.
> 
> 3\. What organization collects the information.
> 
> 4\. How ETR Associates uses the information.
> 
> 5\. With whom ETR Associates may share user information.
> 
> 6\. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
> 
> 7\. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under ETR Associates control.
> 
> 8\. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

Information Collection and Use

The California Tobacco Control Program (CTCP) is the sole owner of the information collected on our web site. ETR Associates collects information at several different points on our Web site. 

Information is collected for the purpose of sales and fulfillment. Users have the option to participate in this activity for the purpose of contacting by email or regular mail. A user must provide the clickstream information (internet protocol address, internet service provider, platform type, date/time stamp, operating system), http protocol information (last url requested and browser type), state management mechanisms (data allowing a user to be tracked consistently), unique identifiers (login id or other id), government-issued identifiers (government issued identifiers), preference data (what you like or dislike), purchase information (purchase payment method and other purchase information), state management mechanisms (data allowing a user to be tracked consistently), unique identifiers (login id or other id), user's name, user's login information, user's employer, organization department user is employed, user's job title, user's business contact information, business/organization name, department/division of business/organization and contact information for the business/organization. The reason we use this information is to archive information for future reference, complete the current transaction, contact by email or regular mail, enhance your experience by customizing our site and understand (in aggregate) interests of website visitors. We retain this information as stated by our business practices. 

Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. You can set your browser to notify you to either accept or deny the cookie according to the following information. 

  * in IE6, see Microsoft's [Internet Explorer Web Privacy](http://www.microsoft.com/windows/ie/evaluation/overview/privacy.asp "How to change your cookie privacy settings in IE6") page. 
  * in Netscape 6, see [Netscape 6 - Safety with More Control](http://home.netscape.com/browsers/6/safety.html "How to change your cookie privacy settings in Netscape 6"). 
  * in Opera 5 or 6, see [Opera Preferences: Privacy](http://www.opera.com/support/resources/privacy.html "How to change your cookie privacy settings in Opera"). 

Our website uses cookies to enhance our site.

Profiles

ETR Associates does not create a user profile. 

Communications from the Site

When customers provide us contact information for Website (user participation is voluntary) we use the information to contact the user to deliver sales and product information that will be useful to the them.

Sharing Information

Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

Personally Identifiable Information  
Information collected for Website is shared with Catalog mailing service. 

Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)  
Information collected for Website is shared with Catalog mailing services.. 

Data Security

ETR Associates has physical security in our facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information. Our company uses secure encryption technology (secure socket connection) for all sensitive financial or health data transmitted on our site.

Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes such as zip code, phone, email or postal address they can change online, physical contact, and other information. If a user wishes to correct/update information or no longer desires our service, they can notify us of what they desire by contacting us using any of the information in the Contact section of this policy.

Links and Advertisements

Our website contains links to other sites. We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. We, ETR Associates, are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Changes to the Privacy Statement

The information you submit to us is controlled by the privacy policy in effect at the time you submit it. If we significantly change our policy, we will post a notice in a conspicuous place on our website notifying visitors of policy changes.

Data Retention Statement

Stated Business Practices Data retention - We keep information about you and your purchases for as long as you remain our customer.

Contact Information

Using the following information, you can contact us if you have questions about our privacy policy. 

> TECC  
> 4 Carbonero Way  
> Scotts Valley, CA 95066   
> USA 
> 
> E-mail: [webmaster@etr.org](mailto:webmaster@etr.org)   
> Phone: +1 831 438 4060 

Resolving Privacy Policy Disputes   
If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, it can be resolved in the following manner.
